<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<section name="1" start="t">
	<p>You are alone in an open boat waiting for death.</p>
	<p>
		How your life has changed since the day that you set out
		from your homeland across the Unbounded Ocean! You had
		signed on aboard a ship in the hope of visiting a dozen ports,
		seeing a thousand wonders. But calamity overtook your voyage
		in the first week, when pirates swooped down upon the vessel.
		You and a handful of shipmates managed to get the cutter down
		into the water and were making off, but some of the pirates leapt
		down from the rail right in your midst. The fighting was hard.
		You remember little of it now, but when it was over the boat
		was awash with blood and you were the only one left alive. Of
		your own ship and the pirates&#8217; there was no sign - the current
		had carried you out of sight of any living thing.
	</p>
	<p>
		Best not to think how you&#8217;ve survived since then. At the
		mercy of the wind and the currents, you have been swept
		steadily westwards into regions completely unknown to you.
		Drinking water has been your biggest problem - you&#8217;ve had to
		rely on rain and there has been none for days. Your body is
		weak, your spirits low. Then, just as death seems ready to draw
		his boat alongside, you see something that kindles new hope.
		White clouds. Birds turning high above. The grey hump of land
		on the horizon!
	</p>
	<p>
		Steering towards the shore, you feel the cutter lurch as it
		enters rough water. The wind whips up plumes of spindrift and
		breakers pound the cliffs. The tiller is yanked out of your hands.
		The little boat is spun around, out of control, and goes plunging
		towards the coast.
	</p>
	<p>
		You leap clear at the last second. There is the snap of timber,
		the roaring crescendo of the waves - and then silence as you go
		under. Striking out wildly, you try to swim clear, then suddenly
		a wave catches you and flings you contemptuously on to the
		beach.
	</p>
	<p>
		You are battered and bedraggled, but alive. Now your
		adventures can begin. <random/>.
	</p>
	<outcomes>
		<outcome range="2-4" section="709"/>
		<outcome range="5-6" section="505"/>
		<outcome range="7" section="714"/>
		<outcome range="8-9" section="313"/>
		<outcome range="10-12" section="151"/>
	</outcomes>
</section>
