<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<section name="198">
	<p>
		<tick codeword="5.Tomb" hidden="t"/>
		You enter the largest of the burial mounds. Inside a large seven-sided chamber is a similarly-shaped plinth, on which seven swords are arranged like spokes, their thin, needle-like blades shining in the darkness. Each sword glows a different colour and seems made of a different material. In the centre of the plinth is a model of seven obelisks.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you step forward, a voice rings in your head: 'I am the champion of the Seven Lords of the Shadar. You are a defiler of their resting place.'
	</p>
	<p>
		Suddenly you are gripped with a raging fever and the strength seems to ebb from your limbs. Some foul sorcery is being used here! Even as you gather yourself to resist, a tall figure steps into view.
	</p>
	<p>
		<difficulty ability="magic" level="13"/>.
		<failure>
			If you fail, you must fight the champion at
			<curse name="Champion's Curse">
				half your COMBAT score
				<effect ability="combat" divide="2"/>
			</curse>
			(round up).
		</failure>
		<success>
			If you succeed you throw off his curse and may fight normally.
		</success>
	</p>
	<fight name="The Champion" combat="8" defence="15" stamina="12"/>
	<p>
		If you lose, <goto section="7" dead="t"/>. If you win, read on.
	</p>
	<p>
		If you were cursed, the
		<lose curse="Champion's Curse">curse is lifted</lose>.
		Return your COMBAT score to normal.
	</p>
	<p>
		You look more carefully at the swords. They seem to represent the elements of some arcane philosophy. They are: the sword of ice, the sword of fire, the sword of stone, the sword of air, the sword of wood, the sword of metal, and the sword of water.
	</p>
	<choices>
		<choice section="223">Take one of the swords (note which one)</choice>
		<choice section="635">Take more than one (note the first one)</choice>
		<choice section="471">Leave without taking a sword</choice>
	</choices>
</section>
