<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<oracleio groupname="Elder Futhark Runes" subclass="Ingrid (Sunny) Halvorsen" classification="GraphicObjTranslations" version="1" language="en" author="Ingrid (Sunny) Halvorsen" >
<entry key="languagename">English</entry>
<entry key="copyright">Copyright © 2007 Ingrid Halvorsen (mailto:sunnyway@aol.com).  Permission is granted to copy, distribute and/or modify this document under the terms of the GNU Free Documentation License, Version 1.2 or any later version published by the Free Software Foundation.  A copy of the license may be found at http://www.gnu.org</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle0">Fehu (F: Domestic cattle, wealth.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning0">Possessions won or earned, earned income, luck. Abundance, financial strength in the present or near future. Sign of hope and plenty, success and happiness. Social success. Energy, foresight, fertility, creation/destruction (becoming).</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle1">Uruz: (U: Auroch, a wild ox.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning1">Physical strength and speed, untamed potential. A time of great energy and health. Freedom, energy, action, courage, strength, tenacity, understanding, wisdom. Sudden or unexpected changes (usually for the better). Sexual desire, masculine potency. The shaping of power and pattern, formulation of the self.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle2">Thurisaz: (TH: Thorn or a Giant.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning2">Reactive force, directed force of destruction and defense, conflict. Instinctual will, vital eroticism, regenerative catalyst. A tendency toward change. Catharsis, purging, cleansing fire. Male sexuality, fertilization. (Thorr, the Thunder god, was of Giant</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle3">Ansuz: (A: The As, ancestral god, i.e. Odin.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning3">A revealing message or insight, communication. Signals, inspiration, enthusiasm, speech, true vision, power of words and naming. Blessings, the taking of advice. Good health, harmony, truth, wisdom.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle4">Raidho: (R: Wagon or chariot.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning4">Travel, both in physical terms and those of lifestyle direction. A journey, vacation, relocation, evolution, change of place or setting. Seeing a larger perspective. Seeing the right move for you to make and deciding upon it. Personal rhythm, world rhythm, dance of life.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle5">Kenaz: (K: Beacon or torch.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning5">Vision, revelation, knowledge, creativity, inspiration, technical ability. Vital fire of life, harnessed power, fire of transformation and regeneration. Power to create your own reality, the power of light. Open to new strength, energy, and power now. Passion, sexual love.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle6">Gebo: (G: Gift.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning6">Gifts, both in the sense of sacrifice and of generosity, indicating balance. All matters in relation to exchanges, including contracts, personal relationships and partnerships.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle7">Wunjo: (W or V: Joy.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning7">Joy, comfort, pleasure. Fellowship, harmony, prosperity. Ecstasy, glory, spiritual reward, but also the possibility of going "over the top". If restrained, the meaning is general success and recognition of worth.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle8">Hagalaz: (H: Hail.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning8">Wrath of nature, destructive, uncontrolled forces, especially the weather, or within the unconscious. Tempering, testing, trial. Controlled crisis, leading to completion, inner harmony.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle9">Nauthiz: (N: Need.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning9">Delays, restriction. Resistance leading to strength, innovation, need-fire (self-reliance). Distress, confusion, conflict, and the power of will to overcome them. Endurance, survival, determination. A time to exercise patience. Recognition of one's fate. Major self-initiated change. Face your fears.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle10">Isa: (I: Ice.) </entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning10">A challenge or frustration. Psychological blocks to thought or activity, including grievances. Standstill, or a time to turn inward and wait for what is to come, or to seek clarity. This rune reinforces runes around it.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle11">Jera: (J or Y: A year, a good harvest.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning11">The results of earlier efforts are realized. A time of peace and happiness, fruitful season. It can break through stagnancy. Hopes and expectations of peace and prosperity. The promise of success earned. Life cycle, cyclical pattern of the universe. Everything changes, in its own time.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle12">Eihwaz: (EI: Yew tree.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning12">Strength, reliability, dependability, trustworthiness. Enlightenment, endurance. Defense, protection. The driving force to acquire, providing motivation and a sense of purpose. Indicates that you have set your sights on a reasonable target and can achieve your goals. An honest man who can be relied upon.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle13">Perthro: (P: Lot cup, vagina.) </entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning13">Uncertain meaning, a secret matter, a mystery, hidden things and occult abilities. Initiation, knowledge of one's destiny, knowledge of future matters, determining the future or your path. Pertaining to things feminine, feminine mysteries including female fertility, and vagina. Good lot, fellowship and joy. Evolutionary change.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle14">Algiz: (Z or -R: Elk, protection.) </entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning14">Protection, a shield. The protective urge to shelter oneself or others. Defense, warding off of evil, shield, guardian. Connection with the gods, awakening, higher life. It can be used to channel energies appropriately. Follow your instincts. Keep hold of success or maintain a position won or earned.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle15">Sowilo: (S: The sun.) </entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning15">Success, goals achieved, honor. The life-force, health. A time when power will be available to you for positive changes in your life, victory, health, and success. Contact between the higher self and the unconscious. Wholeness, power, elemental force, sword of flame, cleansing fire.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle16">Tiwaz: (T: Tyr, the sky god.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning16">Honor, justice, leadership and authority. Analysis, rationality. Knowing where one's true strengths lie. Willingness to self-sacrifice. Victory and success in any competition or in legal matters.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle17">Berkano: (B: Berchta, the birch-goddess.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning17">Birth, general fertility, both mental and physical and personal growth, liberation. Regenerative power and light of spring, renewal, promise of new beginnings, new growth. Arousal of desire. A love affair or new birth. The prospering of an enterprise or venture.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle18">Ehwaz: (E: Horse, two horses.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning18">Transportation. May represent a horse, car, plane, boat or other vehicle. Movement and change for the better. Gradual development and steady progress are indicated. Harmony, teamwork, trust, loyalty. An ideal marriage or partnership. Confirmation beyond doubt the meanings of the runes around it.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle19">Mannaz: (M: Man, mankind.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning19">The Self; the individual or the human race. Your attitude toward others and their attitudes towards you. Friends and enemies, social order. Intelligence, forethought, create, skill, ability. Divine structure, intelligence, awareness. Expect to receive some sort of aid or cooperation now.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle20">Laguz: (L: Water, or a leek.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning20">Flow, water, sea, a fertility source, the healing power of renewal. Life energy and organic growth. Imagination and psychic matters. Dreams, fantasies, mysteries, the unknown, the hidden, the deep, the underworld. Success in travel or acquisition, but with the possibility of loss.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle21">Ingwaz: (NG: Ing, the earth god.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning21">Male fertility, gestation, internal growth. Common virtues, common sense, simple strengths, family love, caring, human warmth, the home. Rest stage, a time of relief, of no anxiety. A time when all loose strings are tied and you are free to move in a new direction. Listen to yourself.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle22">Dagaz: (D: Day or dawn.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning22">Breakthrough, awakening, awareness. Daylight clarity as opposed to nighttime uncertainty. A time to plan or embark upon an enterprise. The power of change directed by your own will, transformation. Hope/happiness, the ideal. Security and certainty. Growth and release. Balance point, the place where opposites meet.</entry>
	<entry key="ObjectTitle23">Othala: (O: Ancestral property.)</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning23">Inherited property or possessions, a house, a home. What is truly important to one. Group order, group prosperity. Land of birth, spiritual heritage, experience and fundamental values. Aid in spiritual and physical journeys. Source of safety, increase and abundance.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning0">Loss of personal property, esteem, or something that you put in effort to keep. It indicates some sort of failure. Greed, burnout, atrophy, discord. Cowardice, stupidity, dullness, poverty, slavery, bondage.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning1">Weakness, obsession, misdirected force, domination by others. Sickness, inconsistency, ignorance. Lust, brutality, rashness, callousness, violence.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning2">Danger, defenselessness, compulsion, betrayal, dullness. Evil, malice, hatred, torment, spite, lies. A bad man or woman. Rape?</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning3">Misunderstanding, delusion, manipulation by others, boredom. Vanity and grandiloquence. (Odin is a mighty, but duplicitous god. He always has his own agenda.)</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning4">Crisis, rigidity, stasis, injustice, irrationality. Disruption, dislocation, demotion, delusion, possibly a death.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning5">Disease, breakup, instability, lack of creativity. Nakedness, exposure, loss of illusion and false hope.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning6">(Gebo cannot be reversed, but may lie in opposition): Greed, loneliness, dependence, over-sacrifice. Obligation, toll, privation, bribery.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning7">Stultification, sorrow, strife, alienation. Delirium, intoxication, possession by higher forces, impractical enthusiasm. Raging frenzy, berzerker.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning8">(Hagalaz cannot be reversed, but may lie in opposition): Natural disaster, catastrophe. Stagnation, loss of power. Pain, loss, suffering, hardship, sickness, crisis.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning9">Constraint of freedom, distress, toil, drudgery, laxity. Necessity, extremity, want, deprivation, starvation, need, poverty, emotional hunger.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning10">(Isa cannot be reversed, but may lie in opposition): Ego-mania, dullness, blindness, dissipation. Treachery, illusion, deceit, betrayal, guile, stealth, ambush, plots.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning11">(Jera cannot be reversed, but may lie in opposition): Sudden setback, reversals. A major change, repetition, bad timing, poverty, conflict.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning12">Confusion, destruction, dissatisfaction, weakness.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning13">Addiction, stagnation, loneliness, malaise.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning14">Hidden danger, consumption by divine forces, loss of divine link. Taboo, warning, turning away, that which repels.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning15">(Sowilo cannot be reversed, but may lie in opposition): False goals, bad counsel, false success, gullibility, loss of goals. Destruction, retribution, justice, casting down of vanity. Wrath of god.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning16">One's energy and creative flow are blocked. Mental paralysis, over-analysis, over-sacrifice, injustice, imbalance. Strife, war, conflict, failure in competition. Dwindling passion, difficulties in communication, and possibly separation.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning17">Family problems and or domestic troubles. Anxiety about someone close to you. Carelessness, abandon, loss of control. Blurring of consciousness, deceit, sterility, stagnation.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning18">This is not really a negative rune. A change is perhaps craved. Feeling restless or confined in a situation. Reckless haste, disharmony, mistrust, betrayal.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning19">Depression, mortality, blindness, self-delusion. Cunning, slyness, manipulation, craftiness, calculation. Expect no help now.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning20">An indication of a period of confusion in your life. You may be making wrong decisions and poor judgements. Lack of creativity and feelings of being in a rut. Fear, circular motion, avoidance, withering. Madness, obsession, despair, perversity, sickness, suicide.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning21">(Ingwaz cannot be reversed, but may lie in opposition): Impotence, movement without change. Production, toil, labor, work.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning22">(Dagaz cannot be reversed, but may lie in opposition): A completion, ending, limit, coming full circle. Blindness, hopelessness.</entry>
	<entry key="ReversedMeaning23">Lack of customary order, totalitarianism, slavery, poverty, homelessness. Bad karma, prejudice, clannishness, provincialism. What a man is bound to.</entry>
</oracleio>

