<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<oracleio groupname="Elder Futhark Runes" subclass="Practical matters" classification="LayoutTranslations" version="1" language="en" author="Aswynn, Northern Mysteries" >
<entry key="languagename">English</entry>
<entry key="copyright">Aswynn, Northern Mysteries</entry>
		<entry key="Title">8 Rune Practical matters</entry>
		<entry key="Description">The Airt (Ætt) of Freya is primarily related to practical and mundane matters. One selects the runes unseen and places them in the area next to the runes already there. These meanings are very simple and on the most basic level serve as the background for a strait forward reading, in which questions of a practical nature can be answered.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle0">Fehu</entry><entry key="Meaning0">Money matters. Psychic energies. Financial strength and prosperity of the present and near future.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle1">Uruz</entry><entry key="Meaning1">Physical health. Vital energies.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle2">Thurisaz</entry><entry key="Meaning2">What opposed you (perhaps physical). Conflicts and complexities of an aggressive nature; psychological problems.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle3">Ansuz</entry><entry key="Meaning3">Sources of inspiration and intellectual expression.  Communications and transmissions; points things back to sources in the past.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle4">Raidho</entry><entry key="Meaning4">Travels - inner or outer. What is right or not right; what move to make; decisions; returns.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle5">Kenaz</entry><entry key="Meaning5">Creativity. Erotic relationships. Opening up of new ways; opportunities; information.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle6">Gebo</entry><entry key="Meaning6">What will be given to you. All matters of an exchanging nature; contracts; personal relationships.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle7">Wunjo</entry><entry key="Meaning7">Relationships, friends. What will give you happiness. Gain; accomplishments; that which is wished for.</entry>
</oracleio>

