<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<oracleio groupname="Elder Futhark Runes" subclass="Relationships" classification="LayoutTranslations" version="1" language="en" author="Aswynn, Northern Mysteries" >
<entry key="languagename">English</entry>
<entry key="copyright">Aswynn, Northern Mysteries</entry>
		<entry key="Title">8 Rune Relationships</entry>
		<entry key="Description">The third airt transcends the two others, in that it largely relates to relationships with other people, and also to the sexual side of life. Whereas the first ætt is largely concerned with the outer world, and the second mainly deals with the inner world, the third ætt synthesized both the inner and outer world, and most of the runes in this ætt contain a dual meaning involving both aspects.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle0">Tiwaz</entry><entry key="Meaning0">Cognitive state. Legal matters. Ideals. Creative energies in the martial sense; where your strengths lie; where to direct your energies in taking initiatives; honor and justice, leadership and authority.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle1">Berkano</entry><entry key="Meaning1">What provides growth and beauty. Fertility; birth' rebirth; growth; maternity; family life; feminine mysteries.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle2">Ehwaz</entry><entry key="Meaning2">With what or whom you should work. Erotic relations. Adaptability; relationships with others; joint efforts; cooperation; sexuality.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle3">Mannaz</entry><entry key="Meaning3">Overall psychic state. Attitude toward death. People at large; attitude toward others; other people's attitudes towards you; legal matters, friends and enemies; intellect.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle4">Laguz</entry><entry key="Meaning4">State of emotional Balance. What will test you. Emotions; stability; imagination; psychic matters; affections.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle5">Ingwaz</entry><entry key="Meaning5">What you should contemplate. Integration; gestation; expectations; progeny.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle6">Dagaz</entry><entry key="Meaning6">Area of unexpected synchronicity. Transmission; opposites; position between light and darkness; initiation; balance between the worlds outside time and space; cosmic consciousness; change from one thing into its opposite; new beginnings.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle7">Othala</entry><entry key="Meaning7">Greater family matters. National or community issues.Home life; country; spiritual heritage; experience; foundation; fundamental values; establishing.</entry>
</oracleio>

