<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<oracleio groupname="Elder Futhark Runes" subclass="Emotional matters" classification="LayoutTranslations" version="1" language="en" author="Aswynn, Northern Mysteries" >
<entry key="languagename">English</entry>
<entry key="copyright">Aswynn, Northern Mysteries</entry>
		<entry key="Title">8 Rune Emotional matters</entry>
		<entry key="Description">The second airt, of Hagalaz, principally corresponds to emotional matters and the psychological conditions present within the individual.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle0">Hagalaz</entry><entry key="Meaning0">Area of possible crisis leading to transformation. The uncontrolled forces in the unconscious, which are usually of a disruptive nature and which usually originate in the past.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle1">Nauthiz</entry><entry key="Meaning1">What resists you (psychically). Source of discontent. Restrictive forces in the unconscious; fears, anxieties; feelings of guilt.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle2">Isa</entry><entry key="Meaning2">What is constraining you. Blocks; stultified conditions; grievances; anything that the individual is not prepared to let go of; the formation of the personality; conditioning.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle3">Jera</entry><entry key="Meaning3">Where rewards can be expected. Relationship with the natural environment. Hopes and expectations; turning points; gradual changes; results of earlier actions.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle4">Eihwaz</entry><entry key="Meaning4">Hidden influences, state of whole being. Relationship with the numinous environment. The driving forces in the unconscious; motivation; sense of purpose.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle5">Perthro</entry><entry key="Meaning5">How you will find joy. The deepest creative part of the unconscious; the hidden realm of higher material that is waiting to come to fruition and birth; hidden talents; occult or psychic abilities.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle6">Algiz</entry><entry key="Meaning6">Thing that needs attention. Way to the gods. The strong protective side in the unconscious; the influence which will protect you; religious aspirations.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle7">Sowilo</entry><entry key="Meaning7">What will guide you. Position of the higher self in relations to the unconscious; the direction in which you will be guided by the higher self; the ability to establish contact between the higher self and the unconscious.</entry>
</oracleio>

