<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<oracleio groupname="Tarot Standard 78 Cards" subclass="Celtic cross" classification="LayoutTranslations" version="1" language="en" author="Thomas Dilts 1960 -" >
<entry key="languagename">English</entry>
<entry key="copyright">Copyright © 2007 Thomas Dilts (tarot@lazy8.nu).  Permission is granted to copy, distribute and/or modify this document under the terms of the GNU Free Documentation License, Version 1.2 or any later version published by the Free Software Foundation.  A copy of the license may be found at http://www.gnu.org</entry>
		<entry key="Title">Celtic Cross</entry>
		<entry key="Description">This is the most common layout and it is best at answering complex questions and it is a good layout even if you aren't even sure what you want to ask.  Like many layouts, this layout is best at answering questions that don't require a choice of one of two alternatives.  If you must use this layout for deciding for one of two alternatives then you should do this layout once for each alternative and then choose the one you think feels best.  Warning though, sometimes the rosiest path is not the best path.  Sometimes the more painful path is the best path.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle0">You, here and now</entry><entry key="Meaning0">This is a one-card description of you and your situation right here and now. All the other cards of the cross (cards 2 to 6) will modify this card telling more details.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle1">Cross-opposite</entry><entry key="Meaning1">This usually shows an aspect that is contrary to the first card.  Often, processes in life are best described by opposites. For instance, "she feels great but hates her job" or "she loves her job but hates her coworkers" or "light is both a particle and a wave" or "she loves humanity but hates people" etc. </entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle2">Subconscious</entry><entry key="Meaning2">What is going on in the subconscious.  What is the root cause of the problem or the reason why you want to ask this question to the tarot.  How your subconscious feels about the situation.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle3">Past</entry><entry key="Meaning3">What has happened before.  How have you been for the last few weeks or months or before the period involved in the question.  What you have already.  What you are bringing with you as bagage to this problem.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle4">Goal</entry><entry key="Meaning4">How you can best work to make sure the situation will be the best for everyone.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle5">Near future</entry><entry key="Meaning5">What will happen in the nearest future.  Usually this is days or at the most, weeks.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle6">Your impressions</entry><entry key="Meaning6">How do you feel in the situation?  Remember, your impressions of the situation may be very different from how the situation is in reality.  How do you see the problem?  How is the problem effecting you?</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle7">External forces</entry><entry key="Meaning7">How do people external to the situation view what is happening and more importantly, how will they effect the situation.  Often, this is an unknown factor that will arise.  Some people say that if a face card appears here then it is refering to a specific person with the sex and personality of the card being the same as the sex and personality of the person who will effect the situation.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle8">Lesson</entry><entry key="Meaning8">The lesson you are meant to learn by this situation.  Perhaps what you need to learn to deal properly with this situation.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle9">Final result</entry><entry key="Meaning9">The end result of the whole question.  How the situation will be resolved in the end.  Althought this can be considered as the most important card of the layout, don't be overly dependent on this card.  The end result may not be so fantastic but maybe you will learn some important lessons or perhaps become stronger and wiser along the way.  Perhaps you simply must experience this situation for your divine plan.  The other cards can give some clues.</entry>
</oracleio>

