<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<oracleio groupname="Tarot Standard 78 Cards" subclass="Twelve Houses Spread (Doane)" classification="LayoutTranslations" version="1" language="en" author="Thomas Dilts" >
<entry key="languagename">English</entry>
<entry key="copyright">Copyright © 2007 Thomas Dilts (tarot@lazy8.nu).  Permission is granted to copy, distribute and/or modify this document under the terms of the GNU Free Documentation License, Version 1.2 or any later version published by the Free Software Foundation.  A copy of the license may be found at http://www.gnu.org</entry>
	<entry key="Title">Twelve Houses Spread (Doane)</entry>
	<entry key="Description"></entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle0">House 1: Appearances </entry><entry key="Meaning0">It can describe our physical appearance or image.
 Something about the individuality of the person. There is an impulsive quality here, where we just are and 
 are immediately recognised by the sign qualities expressed</entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle1">House 10: Career</entry><entry key="Meaning1">highest ambition, usually seen through 
our career, which is how we are recognised and categorised by society. It represents the 
culmination of work and experience to achieve the goals we set ourselves and the authority 
other people invest in us as a result of all our hard work and achievement.</entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle2">House 7: Partnerships</entry><entry key="Meaning2">partnerships and commitment to others 
through marriage or long term relationships. It is opposite the First House and balances the 
needs of us as individuals with those we relate to on a permanent basis. We learn compromise 
and respect for others' individuality which can sometimes take several attempts to achieve! 
It is also traditionally the house of open enemies, and business partnerships</entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle3">House 4: Family</entry><entry key="Meaning3">family, culture and traditions handed down through 
generations and as such can refer to past lives and those who we associate with in this life in order 
to help us work through our soul's purpose</entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle4">House 12: Secrets</entry><entry key="Meaning4"> It may give us cause for doubt and demand 
that we question who we are, but that is its greatest strength. When we withdraw from the 
world and find a place of peace and solitude then we are in a position to commune with 
our higher selves, and planets in the Twelfth show a need for self reflection. Tradtionally 
it was considered the house of seclusion in hospitals, prisons etc..and the domain of secret 
enemies, but we are all capable of being our own worst enemy by failing to nurture our needs.</entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle5">House 9: Religion</entry><entry key="Meaning5">religion, philosophies and belief systems, as 
well as higher education as opposed to school education in the Third House. It is where we 
formulate our code for living, either through our own learning and experience or we can 
adopt our culture's standards</entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle6">House 6: Service</entry><entry key="Meaning6">work and service to the community. It indicates 
how we can be part of society and give our skills to it in order society to benefit, not just ourselves. 
It is also the house associated with health and healing and our ability to maintain our physical 
systems as a cohesive whole</entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle7">House 3: Communication</entry><entry key="Meaning7">the area in our lives where we communicate 
and disseminate information. It is also associated with short journeys and our local environment 
and siblings. It describes our early education, our schooling and is essentially a social house as 
it is where we begin to mee the world in social terms</entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle8">House 11: Society</entry><entry key="Meaning8">special friends and groups of people 
(not family) with whom we feel a common bond or association. There is a recognition 
that other people share our ideals and goals for the common good, perhaps through 
political endeavour or charities. </entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle9">House 8: Transformation</entry><entry key="Meaning9">It is the house of transformation, 
endings and beginnings and the ability to regenerate through sex. It is also associated 
with money and inheritance, and also the partner's money and finances.</entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle10">House 5: Relationships</entry><entry key="Meaning10">experiment with our social skills through 
interacting with friends and lovers. We learn about ourselves through others' reaction too our 
behaviour. Here we are encouraged to express our individuality and creativity and learn not to 
lose our spontaneity and our need for play. So this house also shows hobbies and pastimes and 
also the results of the most creative act, our children</entry>
	<entry key="PositionTitle11">House 2: Material</entry><entry key="Meaning11">what we have in terms of material possessions 
and also our ability to use our special skills and talents to bring our possessions to us. It is the 
House of sustenance and what we must do to maintain our physical well being. It can also indicate 
our self esteem and the value we place not only on material things but also ourselves</entry>
</oracleio>
