<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<oracleio groupname="Elder Futhark Runes" subclass="9 Rune Worldstead" classification="LayoutTranslations" version="1" language="sv" author="Thorsson, Runecaster's Handbook. Aswynn, Northern Mysteries" >
<entry key="languagename">Svenska</entry>
<entry key="copyright">Thorsson, Runecaster's Handbook. Aswynn, Northern Mysteries</entry>
		<entry key="Title">9 Rune Worldstead</entry>
		<entry key="Description">The pattern of the Norse Ættir of the Heavens (which points out North, South, East and West, and the quadrants between) is combined with the other most obvious division of "space", that of the nine worlds of Yggdrasil, to form the Worldstead design used to divide the casting cloth into fields of meaning. In reality, this figure represents the "collapsing" of multidimensional space into a two-dimensional model - as do many sacred symbols of all kinds. The fields are names for the nine worlds of Yggdrasil and derive their meanings from these concepts. (The actual cloth should not have the names of the worlds on it.)</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle0">Niflheim: Nordhr (North).</entry><entry key="Meaning0">That which resists you. Passive or restrictive influences from the outside. Things tending toward dormancy. The deepest part of the shadow in the unconscious. Nifelhel of Niflheim means literally "fog world". Fog is an intangible, insidious state between water and air. All the rejects of the conscious get deposited here. It is the place from which conflicts originate.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle1">Jotunheim: Austr (East)</entry><entry key="Meaning1">That which confuses you. That which may be left to chance. Forces pressing for change. Realm of crisis. Disruptive, raw masculine forces of the unconscious; the destructive male urge; the chaotic part of the self.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle2">Åsgard: Landnordhr (Northeast)</entry><entry key="Meaning2">Higher influences. Nature of relationships with the divinities. The veiled branches of the question. Matters of honor, positive (active) influence from past states of existence ("incarnations:)--ørlög. Individuality. Highest plane. Higher self. Spirituality.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle3">Vanaheim: Vestr (West)</entry><entry key="Meaning3">Promotes growth. Erotic relationships. Persons of the opposite sex. Balancing influences. Forces of continuity, structure, and well being. Feeling (Water).</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle4">Ljóssálfheim: Utnordhr (Northwest)</entry><entry key="Meaning4">Mental influences. Family matters. Messages of Huginn - directions in which you should plan. What will help you. Paths to help you realize influences from Àsgardhr. (Air). Plants, elves, tree spirits and birds are ruled over by Freyr, Lord of the Vanir.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle5">Midgard: Center</entry><entry key="Meaning5">The way people come together to manifest themselves in life. The outcome in life. Ego consciousness. The Personality, Ego Consciousness or Lower self.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle6">Hel: Utsudhr (Southwest)</entry><entry key="Meaning6">Hidden or suppressed instinctual desires. Nature of automatic functions or behaviors. The hidden route of the question. Negative (passive, restrictive) influence from pasts states of existence - ørlög. Destructive part of the Feminine, hidden fourth aspect of the moon; the devouring part of the mother; the half-alive half-dead daughter of Loki, half black, half white.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle7">Svartálfheim: Landsudhr (Southeast)</entry><entry key="Meaning7">Creative emotional influences. Money matters. Messages from Muninn - things you should reflect on. Paths to realize influence from Hel. Sensation (Earth). The Dark Elves are smiths, like Volund, working with minerals, taking base materials from the earth and transmuting them into higher materials.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle8">Muspellsheim: Sudhr (South)</entry><entry key="Meaning8">State of vial energies, that which vitalizes you. Active influences from outside. Things tending toward activity.</entry>
</oracleio>

