<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<oracleio groupname="Elder Futhark Runes" subclass="Seven Runes" classification="LayoutTranslations" version="1" language="sv" author="Aswynn, Northern Mysteries" >
<entry key="languagename">Svenska</entry>
<entry key="copyright">Aswynn, Northern Mysteries</entry>
		<entry key="Title">Seven rune layout</entry>
		<entry key="Description">This runecast gives a bit more detail with more information on how to deal with your problem and on what lead you to your present dilemma in the first place. It usually speaks of events three months into the future and into the past.
If you wish to use this layout but want information on happenings more current than three months, be certain to concentrate on your time frame as well when you are concentrating on your question.
The questions you can answer with this layout can be much broader in scope than with some other runecasts. Instead of asking "yes" or "no" or "what about my relationship?", you can ask questions like "How will my job progress if I take this new business course?" or "If I started seeing other people, how would my current lover accept it?" Through questions like these, you can certainly get enough information to solve all but the most complex problems.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle0">The problem 1</entry><entry key="Meaning0">Your problem as it is now.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle1">The problem 2</entry><entry key="Meaning1">Your problem as it is now.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle2">Past 1</entry><entry key="Meaning2">Factors in the past which have led up to the situations at present</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle3">Past 2</entry><entry key="Meaning3">factors in the past which have led up to the situations at present</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle4">Advice 1</entry><entry key="Meaning4">Runes 5 and 6 are the two most important runes in this runecast. They represent the advise the runes are giving you, and extra special care must be taken to interpret their meanings as they relate to one another. They can indicate a need to wait and not act or a need to act immediately. They also may indicate a total shift of emphasis to new realms totally unrelated to the problem in question.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle5">Advice 2</entry><entry key="Meaning5">Runes 5 and 6 are the two most important runes in this runecast. They represent the advise the runes are giving you, and extra special care must be taken to interpret their meanings as they relate to one another. They can indicate a need to wait and not act or a need to act immediately. They also may indicate a total shift of emphasis to new realms totally unrelated to the problem in question.</entry>
		<entry key="PositionTitle6">Result</entry><entry key="Meaning6">The final position, rune 7, is the result position. Keep in mind that a positive rune in this place (or a negative one, for that matter) will only be truly positive (or negative) if the preceding runes indicate such an outcome</entry>
</oracleio>

