<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<oracleio groupname="Tarot Standard 78 Cards" subclass="ThomasDilts" classification="GraphicObjTranslations" version="1" language="sv" author="Thomas Dilts 1960 -" >
<entry key="languagename">Svenska</entry>
<entry key="copyright">Copyright © 2007 Thomas Dilts (tarot@lazy8.nu).  Permission is granted to copy, distribute and/or modify this document under the terms of the GNU Free Documentation License, Version 1.2 or any later version published by the Free Software Foundation.  A copy of the license may be found at http://www.gnu.org</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle0">0-The Fool</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning0">You feel free from all worldly cares and responsibilities.  You are flowing freely with the stream of life. You are unified with God and His plan for you.  You might be feeling like you have tried everything and now you just "give up" and let God take over.  People around you might think you are irresponsible.  You might be acting so infantile that you are playing "the fool."</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle1">1-The Magician</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning1">You are experiencing a period of power, magic and impulisive activity.  You are so concentrated and active right now that miracles and magic seem to be a common occurance.  Now is a good time to start a new undertaking.  It might be wise to take a moment to look around you to see if you are hurting someone through either neglect or by directly walking over them.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle2">2-The High Priestess</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning2">Trust your intuition! It won't mislead you right now.   You "know" but may not understand how you "know."  You are experiencing intensive dreams and unexplainable feelings.  Let go of the intellect and reasoning for the moment and follow what you are feeling intuitively. You might need to use your intuition to help others as well.  People will listen to your advice even if it may not be logical advice.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle3">3-The Empress</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning3">You have reached a high point of emotional maturity in your life.  You are a central figure giving out unconditional love and emotional support to those around you.  You are in a phase of intensive creativity symbolized by the womb and childbirth.  If there are questions of health then childbirth or the reproductive organs are in focus.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle4">4-The Emperor</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning4">You are in a position of power and authority.   You have worked hard to get where you are and you are experiencing the culmination and possible end of a period in your life. People around you respect you and look up to you as thier protector and leader.  Don't dissapoint them!  Because you are nearing the end of a cycle, you might feel a little dissatisfaction and uneasiness even though you should be experienceing the best times in your life.  </entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle5">5-The Hierophant</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning5">Seek help.  You need perhaps professional help in the form of lawyers, doctors, bankers, counselors, priests or even highly respected friends.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle6">6-The Lovers</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning6">This card always refers to a very close relationship and it usually refers to a relationship that is sexual in nature.  This is a very positive card and the relationship will be very satisying and benificial to both persons.  If the relationship is not sexual then it is still a relationship with lots of deep love.  In very rare cases the card might refer to a deep passion one person has to an idea, hobby, work or way of life.  </entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle7">7-The Chariot</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning7">Stability and sacrifice are keywords.  You need to continue doing what you have started and don't change course or allow doubts to arise. People depend on you and you must not dissapoint them or yourself. Don't change anything!</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle8">8-Strength</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning8">You either are feeling very strong and courageous or you desperately need to start cultivating those qualities to deal with the present situation.  People around you will be inspired by your courage.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle9">9-The Hermit</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning9">Now is a time of reflection and solitude. You might need to rest and reflect on where you are going with your life.  People will see you as the "lonely wolf." You might be feeling very alone and "left out."  This might be a forced exile or a voluntary exile.  Either enjoy this period of isolation or actively seek to break out of it.  </entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle10">10-Wheel of Fortune</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning10">Right now, lady luck is on your side but you probably couldn't care less.  Miracles will happen but at the same time you don't place much importance on these miracles.  There is a certain transformation going on right now in your life which is raining gifts on you and giving you a feeling of understanding of the mysteries of life.  You see the great "circle of life" and feel how life is a continious wheel of birth and death.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle11">11-Justice</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning11">A fair and just solution will come to a situation or problem.  You and/or others will see clearly what has happened.  This is a period of reckoning and all the previously hidden or ignored details will come out for all to see.  Usually this card is positive for you but it might be negative for the other participant of the conflict.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle12">12-The hanged man</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning12">You must take a passive stance at this moment.  You cannot do anything actively to change the situation. Your hands are tied.  It is possible that you will enjoy this moment of passiveness and feel very close to God and the divine plan for you.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle13">13-Death</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning13">Don't misunderstand this card.  Tarot will almost never predict ones death.  This tells of a complete and total change of a situation.  What better symbol for this then "death?"  This change might be difficult to handle but if you show flexibility then this change will usually be greeted with joy in the end.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle14">14-Temperance</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning14">Now is not the time to go to extreams.  Take it easy.  Calm down.  Let life flow and let changes happen.  Small slight changes you make can have a large effect.  Very large efforts you make will probably have no effect at all.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle15">15-The Devil</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning15">You are forced to experience something that you may or may not find enjoyable.  Either way, you have no choice.  It will happen and it will usually happen in a big way.  This can sometimes refer to a relationship you feel unwillingly tied to or it can refer to a very intensive sexual relationship that you are enjoying tremendously.  There is no advice to give you here because the situation is predestined to happen and there is absolutely nothing you can do to stop it, speed it up, or slow it down.  Even if it is something very enjoyable, deep deep down there is an underlying pain that is slowly comming to the surface.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle16">16-The Tower</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning16">Thunder and lightening.  Something intensive and shocking will happen.  You will be totally unprepared.  This will result in a tremendous release of blocked energy.  After the shock is over you will usually be relieved like the calm after the storm.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle17">17-The Star</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning17">All your dreams are coming true.  Whatever you have hoped for is now a reality.  You are fealing elated.  You have a blissful smile on your face.  You feel totally satisifed.  There is nothing more to want at this moment.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle18">18-The Moon</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning18">You have no idea what is happening.  You probably feel that you know what is happening and feel that you have control over the situation but you are deluded.  It is not at all what you think it is.  Right now the smartest thing you can do is to hold your eyes wide open and absolutely make no long term plans, no deals and don't sign any contracts.  Just wait until the situation changes before taking any steps.  If you are forced to take action, then you have to accept the fact that you are acting blindly and will probably make a big mistake.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle19">19-The Sun</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning19">You feel happy and full of energy.  You are burning with enthusiasm and glowing with joy.  You are generously spreading this joy to everyone around you merely by your presence.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle20">20-Judgement</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning20">Now is the time to reap what you have sown.  You or someone must now pay for what they have done.  You cannot escape retribution.  This card is not necesarily negative but it rarely is pointing to a joyous outcome.  At best the outcome is neutral but most often someone will experience some pain when facing what they have done.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle21">21-The World</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning21">This is the last card in the higher arcana and thus represents total fullfillment.  You have reached total illumination.  The situation can not be better in any way, shape or form. The situation has reached its high point and you feel total fullfillment and perhaps the accompanyment of a feeling of oneness with the universe and God.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle22">Ace of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning22">You are intensively experienceing a new feeling or emotion.  A new enterprise is starting involving friends and loved ones.  It can mean the intensive begining of a new relationship.  You are feeling whole and healed and fully prepared to start a new adventure in the field of emotions, feelings and relationships.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle23">Two of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning23">There is a person you call your friend who means very much to you.  You enjoy this persons company greatly and always long to see them again. Nothing right now points to any type of a sexual relationship however, if the stars are willing, it might develop into one eventually.  Perhaps it already was at one time?  This might even be the friendship to an idea, hobby, work, or way of life.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle24">Three of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning24">You have reached a certain level of emotional security where you can freely love yourself and those around.  You enjoy company and may be looking forward to a party of some type.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle25">Four of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning25">You need time to reflect on what it is you feel and want.  You may need to withdraw and meditate a while.  You are experiencing a certain amount of emotional confusion and you look forward to some quiet time to sort things out.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle26">Five of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning26">You are feeling dissapointed with a person or a situation that is near to your heart.  Most likely, you are also being too demanding of the people around you.  This leads to a vicious cirlcle with you being even more dissapointed. Search deeply in yourself to try to find the true source of your sorrow. Perhaps you simply need to get some rest to regain your energy and then to once again be able radiate love to those around you.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle27">Six of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning27">You are feeling sentimental.  You are feeling love inside of yourself and you want to share that love with those around you in small ways.  You desire no big fanfare but just simple tokens of love you want to give to those around you. </entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle28">Seven of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning28">You are in the mood for experimenting with your feelings.  You want to try new relationships, experiences or friends.  You feel like you want to have some fun with something new and different.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle29">Eight of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning29">You need to take an accounting of who you refer to as friends, associates and/or lovers. Most importantly, you need to examine how you feel towards them. You feel tired and worn out emotionally.  Who or what is draining your energy?  A vacation away from it all might be the answer to your problems.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle30">Nine of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning30">You have come to a high point in your emotional development.  You feel mature, secure, loved, and loving towards all.  You are in a position to be a support to those who are not at your level right now.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle31">Ten of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning31">Your circle of friends and your family give you all that you need emotionally and you are a source of strength for them as well. Your happiness is complete.  But, because you have reached the end of a cycle, it might happen that there is a creeping feeling inside that tells you that now it is time to move on to new adventures and lessons.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle32">Page of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning32">You are vulnerable and naive.  Your openness and vulnerability is very charming to those around you.  You feel ready to start a new  relationship or a new enterprise but perhaps you need to mature a little more emotionally first.  Perhaps your feelings for something or someone need to mature a bit before any major action is taken.  You are fully willing to learn from those wiser then you.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle33">Knight of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning33">The time for waiting, wondering or thinking is over.  Now you want to boldly go forward and present what you feel to those around you.  This may mean you want to show your feelings to that somebody special or to present a new idea for a special project you hold dear to your heart.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle34">Queen of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning34">You have reached complete maturity emotionally.  You love yourself and can freely give love and support to others in need.  You feel very loving and protective towards your family and friends.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle35">King of Cups</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning35">You are a central figure giveing emotional support to those around you.  People respect you and depend on you for help when they need it.  You are able to justly demand people around you to behave correctly.  You might have a tendency to be a little inflexible or hard in your views.  The responsibility you bear on your shoulders may seem more of a burden at times.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle36">Ace of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning36">You are begining a new start in the field of health, home, or money.  You feel a tremendous amount of energy streaming through you right now to accomplish a task.  However, this is just the beginning.  You probably don't yet have a complete idea or exact plan about what it is you are going to do. But that is not so important at this moment.  Everything will fall into place soon. </entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle37">Two of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning37">A decision will soon need to be made.  You must decide perhaps between two lifestyles, two paths to take in you business, or decide where to live.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle38">Three of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning38">You are able to see clearly and manage all your resources: money, health and home.  You are able to make good, well-informed decisions about your resources. You will soon be put in a situation where you need to make some deals. Buying and selling.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle39">Four of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning39">You are organizing your resources.  You are working hard towards a specific goal.  Your concentration is good.  You are building a good foundation for the future.  Be careful not to burn yourself out with too much work.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle40">Five of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning40">Your resources are getting strained.  You are feeling that either your money, health or home is in short supply.  There are big changes happening right now with your resources and you are feeling unsure of yourself.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle41">Six of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning41">You are experiencing an abundance of resources right now.  There is one or more associates that you are very generous with.  At this time it is an unbalanced relationship because it is you who are giving and the other is only receiving.  For balance, both must learn to give and take.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle42">Seven of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning42">You want to try new things and experiment with your resources.  You are in a very creative phase right now.  You are taking chances.  Be careful not to risk loosing everything.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle43">Eight of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning43">You are reorganizing your resources right now.  That means a lot of work for you. Your health, home, or work is taking a tremendous amount of your time.  You are trying to find the correct balance for your resources.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle44">Nine of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning44">You material resources have reached a height right now.  You are experiencing excellent health.  Money seems to flow to you and you can maturely see that the money goes to the correct investments.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle45">Ten of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning45">You have reached the end of a phase financially or with some of your resources.  You are experiencing all the material pleasures you want.  Still, you are feeling a little dissatisfied. You are unwilling to take risks that might threaten your stability even even though you know there is a need for a change.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle46">Page of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning46">You are open to begining a new project, education or undertaking.  You will need some more experience or wise help before you can really get underway.  You might be a bit naive or vulnerable with your resources right now.  </entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle47">Knight of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning47">You are now working hard and boldly for what you believe in.  Now is the time to make things happen and to tie up loose ends.  Failure is not an option.  You know what you want and you are willing to go out and get it.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle48">Queen of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning48">Your resources are in perfect balance right now.  You are very financially stable.  Your health is very good.  This usually means a lot of money is on the way and you are able to put the money to good use. </entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle49">King of Pentacles</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning49">You are the one in control of your resources.  Others are depending on you for their support.  You may have a tendency to be a little narrow minded and you might even be a little too frugal (cheap). You have gained a position of power and you must now wield that power wisely.  If this stability is getting boring to you, then you might need to consider starting something new.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle50">Ace of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning50">You are burning for a new idea.  You are intellectually strong and see the relationship between all the different happenings around you.  You know what to do based on your analysis.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle51">Two of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning51">There are two (or more) ideas that are taking up your thoughts right now.  You might need to decide for one or the other.  These ideas might be conflicting.  Perhaps you need to find a balance point between the two ideas?</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle52">Three of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning52">You are organizing your ideas into a comprehensive whole.  Your lifes philosophy is taking form.  Very specifically this card means that your thoughts and feelings are in conflict.  You think one thing yet feel another.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle53">Four of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning53">Now you need to seriously organize your thoughts.  This can only be done through a period of rest and reflection.  You might try meditation or prayer.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle54">Five of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning54">Your ideas are being challanged.  You may feel a desperate need to be in control and will crush anyone in your path.  The fear of failure is usually worse then the failure itself.  What are you holding onto that you need to release.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle55">Six of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning55">Your thoughts are reaching a balance point right now.  You understand what has happened in the past and the future feels secure.  Now is a safe time to take it easy and perhaps a trip or traveling of some sort is in the planning. </entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle56">Seven of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning56">You are experimenting with several ideas.  It is perhaps a little too much happening right now and you may need to cool down so you can focus on a more simpler problem.  Otherwise you are running in circles and getting nothing done.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle57">Eight of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning57">You feel a desperate need to understand a problem or situation yet the solution seems to elude you.  You feel blinded by the problem and all the excessive information.  You feel lost.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle58">Nine of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning58">Your thoughts and ideas are overflowing.  You can't stop thinking about an idea or a problem.  It is keeping you sleepless at nights.  You worry excessively.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle59">Ten of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning59">Your thoughts and ideas are following the same old route.  You have been down this path a million times.  The boredom is so great you may feel really desperate to break out into something different.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle60">Page of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning60">You feel enthusiastic about an idea but feel unsure of yourself as well.  This idea needs some more maturing before it is brought out into the open for public scrutiny.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle61">Knight of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning61">You are burning with passion for your ideas, morals, religion or philosophy.  You want to "save the world."  You can persuade others to accept your ideas.  Nothing can discourage you.  </entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle62">Queen of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning62">You have fully understood a problem or situation.  Your idea or philosopy has reached full maturity and acceptance.  You gladly share your ideas and enlightenment with those near and dear to you.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle63">King of Swords</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning63">You have reached a postion of leadership in an idea, morality, philosophy or religion.  People seek you out for your wisdom.  Your idea may be a little narrow minded.  Perhaps you need to loosen up and show a little more flexibility.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle64">Ace of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning64">You have found a new identity.  You see where you fit into the great scheme of things.  You understand the past and look forward to the future.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle65">Two of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning65">You stand at a crossroad.  Your life can go one way or the other.  You need to make the important decision of which path to take.  You are experiencing the freedom of choice to decide what you want to do with your life.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle66">Three of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning66">You have understood what it is you must do right now.  You see what has happened, all the good and bad.  Your destiny is laid out before you.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle67">Four of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning67">You have worked hard to follow your destiny and now is a time of celibration.  Things simply fall into place.  When you follow your destiny and do your duty as you have been doing, life becomes easy and joyous.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle68">Five of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning68">There are a lot of conflicting wills colliding right now.  Everyone is pulling in a different direction.  You are having a difficult time to get everyone to work together.  Chaos is rampant.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle69">Six of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning69">You have reached a certain balance in your life where you feel fairly confident of who you are and where you are going.  People naturally look up to you and respect your opinions in important matters.  Now you can take some time off for celebrating.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle70">Seven of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning70">You are fighting with the idea of who you are where you come from and where you are going.  You are struggling to find out who you are and where you fit in. You may appear as aggressive to others but your aggression is mostly turned inwards towards yourself.  You might be externalizing this fight towards others as well.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle71">Eight of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning71">Your desiny is taking shape.  It is being reformed and focused.  You are begining to clearly see what life is expecting of you.  You feel fairly certain about your future.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle72">Nine of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning72">You have now fully integrated all the different parts of your life into a comprehensive whole.  You know what is expected of you and you gladly fulfill your duties.  You feel certain about your future.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle73">Ten of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning73">You have been fulfilling your destiny and duties faithfully but now it is becomming a burden.  You feel too much is expected of you and you are starting to buckle under the stress.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle74">Page of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning74">You are just starting out on your lifes path.  You are not too sure about who you are or where you are going but that does not matter.  You are open and williing to learn and to change when necessary.  You are actively seeking your destiny but have not yet found it.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle75">Knight of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning75">You feel sure about yourself and you know what you want.  You accept your destiny and you are determined to fullfill it.  You do your duty faithfully.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle76">Queen of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning76">You have found your place in life.  You are happy and fulfilled.  You fulfill your duties and that gives you great satisfaction.  You are a source of strength for family and friends.</entry>
		<entry key="ObjectTitle77">King of Wands</entry><entry key="ObjectMeaning77">You have come into a postion of leadership for either your friends, family, work, religion or society. It is a tremendous responsibility but you are prepared for the challange. People look up to you and are willing to follow you.</entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning0"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning1"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning2"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning3"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning4"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning5"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning6"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning7"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning8"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning9"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning10"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning11"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning12"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning13"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning14"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning15"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning16"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning17"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning18"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning19"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning20"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning21"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning22"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning23"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning24"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning25"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning26"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning27"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning28"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning29"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning30"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning31"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning32"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning33"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning34"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning35"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning36"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning37"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning38"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning39"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning40"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning41"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning42"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning43"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning44"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning45"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning46"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning47"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning48"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning49"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning50"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning51"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning52"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning53"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning54"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning55"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning56"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning57"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning58"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning59"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning60"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning61"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning62"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning63"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning64"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning65"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning66"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning67"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning68"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning69"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning70"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning71"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning72"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning73"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning74"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning75"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning76"></entry>
		<entry key="ReversedMeaning77"></entry>
</oracleio>

