<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<section name="49">
	<p>
		Donations have been streaming into the shrine lately. As the overlord of the battlefield, Juntoku is very popular with soldiers - especially now, on the eve of civil war.
	</p>
	<p>
		The courtyard of the shrine is fined with flocks of well-fed pigeons, the special messengers of the god. You look around for a priest, finally catching the eye of a slight youth in a long-sleeved white robe.
	</p>
	<p>&#8216;Just leave a donation and tell the god what you want,&#8217; he says.</p>
	<p>
		To obtain a blessing requires you to
		<difficulty ability="charisma" level="15" force="f">
			make a CHARISMA roll at a Difficulty of 15<adjust god="Juntoku" amount="3"/>
		</difficulty>, or a Difficulty of 12 if you are an initiate of Juntoku.
		<failure>
			If you fail the CHARISMA roll you
			<lose blessing="*">lose all your current blessings</lose>.
		</failure>
		<success>
			On a successful roll Juntoku gives you a blessing:
			write <tick blessing="combat"/>
			in the Blessings box on your Adventure Sheet. The blessing works by allowing you to try again when you fail a COMBAT roll. You can use the blessing only once; it is then used up and you should cross it off. Also, you can have only one COMBAT blessing at any one time.
		</success>
	</p>
	<p>
		<if safeAddGod="Juntoku"><if shards="50">
				To become an initiate you must pay a donation of
				<lose shards="50" price="x"/>,
				and you can then
				<tick god="Juntoku" flag="x">write Juntoku</tick> in the God box on your Adventure Sheet.
		</if></if>
		You must not already be an initiate of another god.
		<if god="Juntoku"><if shards="40">
				(If you were already an initiate of Juntoku and want to renounce that status now, pay compensation of
				<group>
					<text>40 Shards</text>
					<lose shards="40"/>
					<lose god="Juntoku"/>
				</group>
				to avoid the god&#8217;s wrath.)
		</if></if>
	</p>
	<p>When you have finished your devotions, <goto section="178"/>.</p>
</section>
